myfoodandhappiness.com 2019-07-01

# Privacy Policy - My Food & Happiness

Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

**What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our website?**

We use cookies, please read further below more details about cookies. Also, when posting comments, you will be asked to enter your name and email address.

**When do we collect information?**

We collect information from you when you subscribe to a newsletter or you enter a comment.

The data we collect is compliant with the Data Protection Act 1988.

When you subscribe to our email newsletter, we will use this information to stay in touch with you and provide occasional updates and marketing. Your personal details will be stored by our email automation platform – Mail Chimp in accordance with their [Privacy Policy](https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/) & [Terms.](https://mailchimp.com/legal/terms/)

**How do we use your information?**

We may use the information we collect from you when you sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

The email address you provide may be used to send you periodically information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

At the bottom of each and every email sent to you, there is an unsubscribe link. If you click that link, you will never hear from us again.

We will never share your email address with anyone.

**How do we protect visitor information?**

We do not use an SSL certificate as we only provide articles and information, and we never ask for personal or private information.

**Do we use ‘cookies’?**

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site’s or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

**We use cookies to:**  
• Keep track of advertisements.  
• Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third party services that track this information on our behalf.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser’s Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

**Cookies opt out**

You can opt out from Google ads cookies by going to the following page: [https://www.google.com/settings/ads/plugin/ ](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/plugin)

Finally, you can choose to disable or selectively turn off cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings.

**Third Party Disclosure**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Google**

Google’s advertising requirements can be summed up by Google’s Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en

We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

We have implemented the following:  
• Demographics and Interests Reporting

We along with third-party vendors, such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions, and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.

Opting out:  
Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising initiative opt out page or permanently using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may [contact us here](http://www.myfoodandhappiness.com/contact/).

Last Edited on 2018-24-05
